

ABOUT ME

I have worked as a project manager in creative agencies for over 10 years. I have managed store design, brand identity, strategic, brand guardianship and guidelines projects which have given me diverse and transferable experience.

I have strong administrative skills that include proposal writing, fee scoping, budgets, timelines, resourcing talent, briefing teams, invoicing and prioritising tasks. I am also Microsoft Office and Keynote proficient. I am able to work on multiple workstreams and can adapt in fast paced environments.

I have experience liaising with multiple stakeholders and have worked with clients of all levels of seniority. I have been responsible for providing project updates to stakeholders, facilitating meetings and following up with minutes.

I'm a calm, approachable, helpful and humble worker. I'm easy to get along with and work well both independently and as part of a team. I have experience working closely with multidisciplinary teams that have comprised of strategists, 3D and 2D designers as well as other specialists.

References are available upon request.

TRISTAN DAUVERGNE

SJÖVIKSVÄGEN 76, 11757 STOCKHOLM +46 (0) 79 337 7897 TRISTAN.DAUVERGNE@GMAIL.COM

EXPERIENCE

CLIENT / PROJECT MANAGER HOUSEHOLD DESIGN. LONDON (MAY 2017 - NOV 2018)

Client / Project Manager for clients including Christian Louboutin, Kier Group and Ludlow Farms

I was responsible for projects with small to medium sized budgets that included store design, strategic insight and identity

Highlights from Household include working with a team on the concept design through to design intent for over 20 new Christian Louboutin stores around the world, and the design of the new Ludlow Farms master identity, sub-brand identities and guidelines

CLIENT / PROJECT MANAGER

CONRAN DESIGN GROUP, LONDON (JAN 2016 - MAY 2017)

Client / Project Manager as part of a dedicated Shell team

I was responsible for Shell's global brand guardianship service. The service handled an average of 50 retail brand related enquiries a month from Shell's global stakeholders

Part of managing this service included facilitating weekly update calls and producing quarterly reports with analysis for the client

I was the project manager for the first Shell SELECT 'Gen 5' formats in Asia. This involved managing a multidisciplinary team of strategists and designers starting from a strategic platform, through the design stages and then technical drawings for contractors

CLIENT / PROJECT MANAGER ENDPOINT, LONDON (JULY 2014 - DEC 2015)

Client / Project Manager for wayfinding and brand implementation projects. Clients were Nike Factory Stores, Westminster University and London Bridge Hospital

I was responsible for managing site audits for Nike Factory Stores at their new locations across the UK and Europe and increase awareness of the Nike Factory Store brand

I managed all project aspects including timelines, budgets, travel logistics and client feedback

Guidelines were then developed to inform site negotiations and improve the presence of the NFS brand in the future

ACCOUNT / PRODUCTION MANAGER SEEN DISPLAYS. LONDON (JAN 2014 - JUNE 2014)

Account Manager for Karen Millen

I managed the production and logistics of the Karen Millen A/W 14 windows. I worked closely with an external manufacturer, managing prototyping, quality control and timelines to ensuring the window displays were produced on time and budget

At Seen Displays, I also managed the design, production and logistics of Karen Millen's S/S 15 press day as well as the display materials for their new flagship store in Knightsbridge

INTERN TO ACCOUNT MANAGER EVERYBODY ENGAGE. LONDON (JULY 2007 - DEC 2013)

Account Manager for clients including AEG, BODY WORLDS, LOWE + Partners, Tate Modern

I handled the marketing timelines for the Tutankhamn, BODY WORLDS and Titanic exhibitions all at the O2 as well as marketing partnerships, events, production of radio advertising and the design of print collateral and promotional material

I also managed events including an event for the Tate Modern and Damien Hirst in Covent Garden. In addition to managing all logistics of the public event, I was stakeholder liaison between the client, PR agency, charity partner and local authorities

EDUCATION

BA THEATRE: DESIGN FOR PERFORMANCE
UAL: CENTRAL ST. MARTIN'S, LONDON (SEP 2004 - JULY 2007)

FOUNDATION STUDIES IN ART & DESIGN UAL: CENTRAL ST. MARTIN'S, LONDON (SEP 2003 - JULY 2004)

HIGH SCHOOL & FURTHER EDUCATION
HOLY FAMILY TECHNOLOGY COLLEGE (SEP 1996 - JULY 2003)

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH: NATIVE SPOKEN AND WRITTEN
FRENCH: BASIC SPOKEN AND WRITTEN
SWEDISH: D LEVEL SFI